## Nadya Wilkinson II

4001 Inglewood Avenue, Redondo Beach, CA, 90278 (424) 237-5528 nadyawilk@gmail.com

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Five years of experience in a finance setting Excellent interpersonal and communication skills

Knowledge of US GAAP

Proficiency using QuickBooks, Birch Street, Sage 100/Intacct, Oracle, SAP, Yardi, Microsoft Dynamics (Nav, Solomon, Great Plains), Microsoft Office, Juniper

Square, Xero Certified

## **EXPERIENCE**

Staff Accountant, Kirkwood Collection, Inc, June 2018 – Current

Prepare and post, accurate and timely journal entries, maintaining supporting documentation

Submitted and prepared loan draw requests/requested additional funds Multi entity analyzation of monthly property financials and performance metrics in pursuit of improving cash flow and investment returns

Produced month end schedules including: Fixed assets, prepaid expenses, deposits, accruals and liability accounts ensuring proper coding and recording monthly amortizing or depreciation

Preparing and publishing financial statements

Processed multi-property payroll & cut payroll costs by 15%

**Accounting Assistant,** ANR Industries, February 2018 to June 2018 (Temporary)

Reconciled job costs for multiple entities against GL

Ensured timely payment to subcontractors and vendors, plus expense vouchers Processed construction loan draw requests for current open projects Knowledge of Lien Management, prelims, and lien laws in California FP & A duties

**General Accountant,** W Hollywood Hotel, Hollywood, CA, June 2017 to February 2018

Educated management on strategies for minimizing excessive account accruals Slashed Food and Beverage costs by 30% by negotiating pricing and fees while ensuring the continuation of enhancements of service

Collaborated with the Director of Finance on month end projects Obtained proper documentation for new vendors (W8 & W9)

Trained new hires on company's software and ensured their attention to detail

Junior Accountant, Luxury Shipping Lines, Torrance, CA, July 2014 to June 2017

Prepared the daily deposit and cash reconciliation journal

Stopped fraud on three overseas accounts

Three-way matching of purchase orders

Budget forecast analysis and planning

## **Education**

University of California Riverside, Riverside, CA

Major: Economics - Degree completion: May 2020

Santa Monica College, Santa Monica, CA

Completed two semesters of accounting courses

Associates of Science General Science